<resources>
    <string name="floodwhat">
        WHAT TO DO WHEN FLOOD COMES:
    </string>
    <string name="landwhat">
        WHAT TO DO WHEN LANDSLIDE COMES:
    </string>
    <string name="volcwhat">
        WHAT TO DO WHEN VOLCANIC ERRUPTION COMES:
    </string>
    <string name="typhoontodo">
    Stay inside the house.
    Always keep yourself updated with the latest weather report.
    If there is a need to move to an evacuation center, follow these reminders.
    Evacuate calmly.
    Close the windows and turn off the main power switch.
    Put important appliances and belongings in a high ground.
    Avoid the way leading to the river.

    </string>
    <string name="floodtodo">
    Be Alert
    Don’t drive unless you have to.If you must drive, travel with care
    NEVER drive through flooded roadways. STOP! Turn Around Don’t Drown.
    Get to high ground – Climb to safety!
    Evacuate immediately, if you think you are at risk or are advised to do so!
    Put important appliances and belongings in a high ground.

    </string>

    <string name="landtodo">
    Listen to local news stations on a battery-powered radio for warnings of heavy rainfall.
    Listen for unusual sounds that might indicate moving debris, such as trees cracking or boulders knocking together.
    Move away from the path of a landslide or debris flow as quickly as possible. Look upstream before crossing a bridge and do not cross the bridge if a mudflow is approaching.
    Avoid river valleys and low-lying areas.

    </string>
    <string name="volctodo">
    Listen for emergency information and alerts.
    Follow evacuation or shelter orders. If advised to evacuate, then do so early.
    Avoid areas downstream of the eruption.
    Protect yourself from falling ash.
    Do not drive in heavy ash fall.

    </string>
    <string name="app_name">FinalsProject_Ignacio_Lucero</string>
    <string name="title">iCare</string>
    <string name="button1">Let us Get Started</string>
    <string name="title2">Disaster List </string>
    <string name="typhoon">Typhoon</string>
    <string name="landslide">Land Slide</string>
    <string name="volcanic">Volcanic Erruption</string>
    <string name="flood">Flood</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="flooddes">
        A flood is an overflow of water that submerges land that is usually dry.
    </string>
    <string name="typhoondes">
        A typhoon is a mature tropical cyclone that develops between 180° and 100°E in the Northern Hemisphere. 
    </string>
    <string name="volcanicdes">
       A volcanic eruption occurs when hot materials from the earth's interior are thrown out of a volcano.
     </string>
    <string name="landdes">
        A landslide is defined as the movement of a mass of rock, debris, or earth down a slope.
    </string>
    <string name="buttonwhat">What To Do</string>
    <string name="buttonbring">What to Bring</string>
    <string name="typhoonwhat">WHAT TO DO WHEN TYPHOON COMES:
    </string>

</resources>
